onlinemoneybloggers.com 2012-10-05

# Privacy - Online Money Bloggers

Privacy Policy for OnlineMoneyBloggers.com

The privacy of our visitors to Online Money Bloggers is important to us.

At Online Money Bloggers, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit Online Money Bloggers, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell or give your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

  * Google’s use of the DART cookie
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [ **Google ad and content network privacy policy**](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/).

We also use third party advertisements on Online Money Bloggers to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies, DART cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. Use of cookies is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). The use of DART cookies enables advertisers such as Google Adsense to serve ads based on your visit and your visits to other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by [ **visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy**](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

## My comment policy:

1\. Readers are solely responsible and liable for their comments.  
2. We will not publish comments we personally don’t understand (e.g. written in a different language), are irrelevant or are considered spam.  
3\. By commenting, you grant Online Money Bloggers license to use, modify, and delete all comments.  
4\. Link backs made by commercial sites may be deleted.  
5\. Policy subject to change at any time.  
6\. Reader questions to my email box may be reprinted and used as the subject matter in posts.
